{
"title":"Instant Messaging Questions",
"lastUpdate":"27/1/2018",
"categoryId": 0,
"data":[
        {
      "question":"AFK",
      "answer":"away from the keyboard",
      "categoryId": 0,
      "id":379
        },
        {
      "question":"A/S/L",
      "answer":"Age/Sex/location",
      "categoryId": 0,
      "id":897
        },
        {
      "question":"ASAP",
      "answer":"As Soon As Possible",
      "categoryId": 0,
      "id":12
        },
        {
      "question":"ATM",
      "answer":"At The Moment",
      "categoryId": 0,
      "id":23
        },
        {
      "question":"A3",
      "answer":"Anytime Anywhere Anyplace",
      "categoryId": 0,
      "id":3
        },
        {
      "question":"BBL",
      "answer":"Be Back Later",
      "categoryId": 0,
      "id":15
        },
        {
      "question":"BBS",
      "answer":"Be Back Soon",
      "categoryId": 0,
      "id":530
        },
        {
      "question":"BBQ",
      "answer":"Barbecue",
      "categoryId": 0,
      "id":5
        },
        {
      "question":"B4N",
      "answer":"Bye For Now",
      "categoryId": 0,
      "id":70
        },
        {
      "question":"BRB",
      "answer":"Be Right Back",
      "categoryId": 0,
      "id":48
        },
        {
      "question":"BRT",
      "answer":"Be Right There",
      "categoryId": 0,
      "id":59
        },
        {
      "question":"BTW",
      "answer":"By The Way",
      "categoryId": 0,
      "id":66
        },
        {
      "question":"CU",
      "answer":"See You",
      "categoryId": 0,
      "id":23
        },
        {
      "question":"CYA",
      "answer":"See You",
      "categoryId": 0,
      "id":28
        },
        {
      "question":"CUZ",
      "answer":"because",
      "categoryId": 0,
      "id":99
        },
        {
      "question":"EM",
      "answer":"email",
      "categoryId": 0,
      "id":102
        },
        {
      "question":"FAV",
      "answer":"favourite",
      "categoryId": 0,
      "id":120
        },
        {
      "question":"DND",
      "answer":"Do not Disturb",
      "categoryId": 0,
      "id":176
        },
        {
      "question":"EOF",
      "answer":"End of life",
      "categoryId": 0,
      "id":205
        },
        {
      "question":"FAQ",
      "answer":"Frequently asked questions",
      "categoryId": 0,
      "id":270
        },
        {
      "question":"FTL",
      "answer":"For the loss",
      "categoryId": 0,
      "id":295
        },
        {
      "question":"FTW",
      "answer":"For the win",
      "categoryId": 0,
      "id":350
        },
        {
      "question":"FYI",
      "answer":"For your information",
      "categoryId": 0,
      "id":495
        },
        {
      "question":"FB",
      "answer":"Facebook",
      "categoryId": 0,
      "id": 495
      },{
      "question":"F2F",
      "answer":"face to face",
      "categoryId": 0,
      "id": 495
      },{
      "question":"FWD",
      "answer":"forward",
      "categoryId": 0,
      "id": 495
      },{
      "question":"GTG",
      "answer":"Got to Go",
      "categoryId": 0,
      "id": 495
      },{
      "question":"G9",
      "answer":"Genius",
      "categoryId": 0,
      "id": 495
      },{
      "question":"GBTW",
      "answer":"Get back to work",
      "categoryId": 0,
      "id": 495
      },{
        "question": "GF",
        "answer": "girlfriend",
        "categoryId": 0,
        "id": 495
    }
      ,{
      "question":"GFU",
      "answer":"Good for you",
      "categoryId": 0,
      "id": 495
      },{
      "question":"GRATS",
      "answer":"Congratulations",
      "categoryId": 0,
      "id": 495
      },{
      "question":"GM",
      "answer":"Good Morning",
      "categoryId": 0,
      "id": 495
      },{
      "question":"GN",
      "answer":"Good Night",
      "categoryId": 0,
      "id": 495
      },{
      "question":"HAND",
      "answer":"Have A Nice Day",
      "categoryId": 0,
      "id": 495
      },{
      "question":"HF",
      "answer":"Have fun",
      "categoryId": 0,
      "id": 495
      },{
      "question":"HT",
      "answer":"hat tip",
      "categoryId": 0,
      "id": 495
      },{
      "question":"HTH",
      "answer":"hope that helps",
      "categoryId": 0,
      "id": 495
      },{
      "question":"IIRC",
      "answer":"if I remember correctly",
      "categoryId": 0,
      "id": 495
      },{
      "question":"IRL",
      "answer":"in real life",
      "categoryId": 0,
      "id":495
        },
        {
      "question":"IC",
      "answer":"I See",
      "categoryId": 0,
      "id": 495
        },
        {
      "question":"ICQ",
      "answer":"I Seek you",
      "categoryId": 0,
      "id": 495
        },
        {
      "question":"IM",
      "answer":"Instant Messenger",
      "categoryId": 0,
      "id": 495
        },
        {
      "question":"JK",
      "answer":"Just Kidding",
      "categoryId": 0,
      "id": 495
        },
        {
      "question":"KISS",
      "answer":"Keep it simple stupid",
      "categoryId": 0,
      "id": 495
        },
        {
      "question":"LI",
      "answer":"LinkedIn",
      "categoryId": 0,
      "id": 495
        },
        {
      "question":"LDR",
      "answer":"Long Distance Relationship",
      "categoryId": 0,
      "id": 495
        },
        {
      "question":"LMAO",
      "answer":"Laugh My Ass Off",
      "categoryId": 0,
      "id": 495
      },{
      "question":"LOL",
      "answer":"Laughing Out Loud",
      "categoryId": 0,
      "id": 495
        },
        {
      "question":"LTNS",
      "answer":"Long Time No See",
      "categoryId": 0,
      "id": 495
        },
        {
      "question":"L8R",
      "answer":"Later",
      "categoryId": 0,
      "id": 495
        },
        {
      "question":"IC",
      "answer":"I See",
      "categoryId": 0,
      "id": 495
        },
        {
      "question":"M/F",
      "answer":"Male/Female",
      "categoryId": 0,
      "id": 495
        },
        {
      "question":"MSG",
      "answer":"message",
      "categoryId": 0,
      "id": 495
        },
        {
      "question":"M8",
      "answer":"skate",
      "categoryId": 0,
      "id": 495
        },
        {
      "question":"NE1",
      "answer":"Anyone",
      "categoryId": 0,
      "id": 495
        },
        {
      "question":"NP",
      "answer":"No Problem",
      "categoryId": 0,
      "id": 495
        },
        {
      "question":"OIC",
      "answer":"Oh I See",
      "categoryId": 0,
      "id": 495
        },
        {
      "question":"OS",
      "answer":"Operating System",
      "categoryId": 0,
      "id": 495
        },
        {
      "question":"OMG",
      "answer":"oh my God",
      "categoryId": 0,
      "id": 495
        },
        {
      "question":"PLZ",
      "answer":"please",
      "categoryId": 0,
      "id": 495
        },
{
"question":"PPL",
"answer":"people",
"categoryId": 0,
"id": 495
} ,{
"question":"RIP",
"answer":"rest in peace",
"categoryId": 0,
"id": 495
} ,{
"question":"S2PID",
"answer":"stupid",
"categoryId": 0,
"id": 495
} ,{
"question":"SD",
"answer":"sweet dreams",
"categoryId": 0,
"id": 495
} ,{
"question":"SEC",
"answer":"second",
"categoryId": 0,
"id": 495
} ,{
"question":"SK8",
"answer":"skate",
"categoryId": 0,
"id": 495
} ,{
"question":"SOME1",
"answer":"someone",
"categoryId": 0,
"id": 495
} ,{
"question":"SPOZ",
"answer":"suppose",
"categoryId": 0,
"id": 495
} ,{
"question":"SRY",
"answer":"sorry",
"categoryId": 0,
"id": 495
} ,{
"question":"SS",
"answer":"so sorry",
"categoryId": 0,
"id": 495
} ,{
"question":"STR8",
"answer":"Straight",
"categoryId": 0,
"id": 495
} ,{
"question":"SU",
"answer":"shut up",
"categoryId": 0,
"id": 495
} ,{
"question":"SYS",
"answer":"see you soon",
"categoryId": 0,
"id": 495
} ,{
"question":"SUP",
"answer":"Whats Up",
"categoryId": 0,
"id": 495
} ,{
"question":"SYL",
"answer":"See you later",
"categoryId": 0,
"id": 495
} ,{
"question":"THX",
"answer":"Thank You",
"categoryId": 0,
"id": 495
} ,{
"question":"OH",
"answer":"overheard",
"categoryId": 0,
"id": 495
} ,{
"question":"TYVM",
"answer":"thank you very much",
"categoryId": 0,
"id": 495
},
{
"question":"TTYL",
"answer":"Talk To You Later",
"categoryId": 0,
"id": 495
} ,{
"question":"TG",
"answer":"Thats great",
"categoryId": 0,
"id": 495
} ,{
"question":"TOS",
"answer":"Terms of service",
"categoryId": 0,
"id": 495
} ,{
"question":"TC",
"answer":"Take Care",
"categoryId": 0,
"id": 495
} ,{
"question":"U",
"answer":"You",
"categoryId": 0,
"id": 495
} ,{
"question":"U4E",
"answer":"Yours For Ever",
"categoryId": 0,
"id": 495
} ,{
"question":"WB",
"answer":"Welcome Back",
"categoryId": 0,
"id": 495
} ,{
"question":"W8",
"answer":"Wait",
"categoryId": 0,
"id": 495
} ,{
"question":"YW",
"answer":"you are welcome",
"categoryId": 0,
"id": 495
} ,{
"question":"LMK",
"answer":"Let me know",
"categoryId": 0,
"id": 495
} ,{
"question":"POS",
"answer":"Parents Over shoulder",
"categoryId": 0,
"id": 495
} ,{
"question":"WTH",
"answer":"What the hell",
"categoryId": 0,
"id": 495
} ,{
"question":"SOS",
"answer":"Someone on Shoulder",
"categoryId": 0,
"id": 495
} ,{
"question":"TTYL",
"answer":"Talk to you later",
"categoryId": 0,
"id": 495
},{
"question":"BFF",
"answer":"Best Friends forever",
"categoryId": 0,
"id": 495
} ,{
"question":"BMT",
"answer":"Before my time",
"categoryId": 0,
"id": 495
},
{
"question":"ASAIC",
"answer":"As soon as I can",
"categoryId": 0,
"id": 495
} ,{
"question":"JFY",
"answer":"Just for you",
"categoryId": 0,
"id": 495
} ,{
"question":"1NAM",
"answer":"One in a million",
"categoryId": 0,
"id": 495
} ,{
"question":"ROFL",
"answer":"Rolling on Floor laughing",
"categoryId": 0,
"id": 495
} ,{
"question":"ROTF",
"answer":"Rolling on The Floor",
"categoryId": 0,
"id": 495
} ,{
"question":"B4N",
"answer":"Bye for now",
"categoryId": 0,
"id": 495
} ,{
"question":"404",
"answer":"No clue",
"categoryId": 0,
"id": 495
} ,{
"question":"4EVA",
"answer":"Forever",
"categoryId": 0,
"id": 495
} ,{
"question":"BOT",
"answer":"Back on Topic",
"categoryId": 0,
"id": 495
},
{
"question":"PMSL",
"answer":"Pissing myself laughing",
"categoryId": 0,
"id": 495
},
{
"question":"YSIC",
"answer":"Why should I care",
"categoryId": 0,
"id": 495
},
{
"question":"WRU",
"answer":"Where are you",
"categoryId": 0,
"id": 495
},
{
"question":"WOA",
"answer":"Work of Art",
"categoryId": 0,
"id": 495
}

    ]
}